<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on 문화기술 이슈 매거진</title>
    <link>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on 문화기술 이슈 매거진</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:01:35 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Minimalist Design is Shaping the Future of Web Aesthetics</title>
      <link>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/minimalist-design-is-shaping-the-future-of-web-aesthetics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/minimalist-design-is-shaping-the-future-of-web-aesthetics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent years, minimalist design has become a defining trend in web aesthetics. As websites continue to evolve, the desire for clean, simple, and intuitive design has grown significantly. Minimalism, with its focus on essential elements and decluttered interfaces, has emerged as a powerful approach to creating visually appealing and user-friendly digital experiences. It’s not just a passing trend; minimalist design is shaping the future of web aesthetics by putting clarity and usability at the forefront.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Elements That Make a Design Endure Across Decades</title>
      <link>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/exploring-the-elements-that-make-a-design-endure-across-decades/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/exploring-the-elements-that-make-a-design-endure-across-decades/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In the fast-paced world of design, trends come and go, often leaving a trail of dated aesthetics in their wake. Yet, some designs stand the test of time, maintaining their appeal and functionality across decades. What makes certain designs endure while others fade into obscurity? Timeless design is more than just a look—it&amp;rsquo;s a thoughtful blend of functionality, simplicity, and cultural resonance that transcends changing tastes. Understanding the elements that contribute to lasting design can help designers create work that remains relevant and captivating, year after year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Color to Influence Emotions and Behaviors</title>
      <link>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/how-to-use-color-to-influence-emotions-and-behaviors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/how-to-use-color-to-influence-emotions-and-behaviors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Color is a powerful tool in shaping our perceptions, emotions, and even behaviors. Whether in design, marketing, art, or everyday life, colors can evoke specific feelings and influence how we interact with the world around us. From the calming blues that can soothe anxiety to the energizing reds that can grab attention, understanding the psychology of color enables us to make deliberate choices that affect mood and decision-making. By harnessing the emotional impact of colors, we can create environments, brands, and experiences that connect more deeply with people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>디지털 아바타, 새로운 문화 인터페이스가 되다</title>
      <link>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/processing-power-is-moving-closer-to-the-source-of-data-for-faster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 15:01:35 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kcti111.github.io/magazine/posts/processing-power-is-moving-closer-to-the-source-of-data-for-faster/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Historically, data processing has relied on centralized cloud data centers that store, analyze, and process information from all over the globe. However, this approach introduces a delay—known as latency—when sending data back and forth over long distances. As applications become more time-sensitive, even milliseconds can make a significant difference, particularly in fields like healthcare and smart manufacturing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edge computing is the bridge between the digital and physical worlds, making everything smarter, faster, and more responsive.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
